https://www.barium.se/en/terms

Login
Product
Resources
Resources
Your knowledge source for everything related to business development and digitization
Knowledge Library
E-books, white paper, guides, customer cases - all gathered in one place
Support
Our dedicated support team is here to help you
Professional services and training
Digitize and improve your business faster with the help of our experts
Helpcenter (external)
Updated agreements August 2020
DPA is an integral part of the Agreement (GT&C)
The current text of the agreement governing the processing of personal data is being supplemented with a written DPA (Data Processor Agreement). This DPA governs how Barium, as a processor of personal data, processes the personal data which you as a customer and the controller of personal data choose to process in our platform. We have produced a data processor agreement, which is well balanced and adapted to the Barium Live service. This DPA applies automatically and thus no extra approval is required.
Updated DPA aug 2020
The European Court of Justice decided in June 2020 to declare the Privacy Shield invalid as an adequate protection mechanism for 3rd country's transfers of personal data to the United States. Barium has acted on this and has introduced the EU's approved standard contract clauses in the Data protection amendments with each subcontractor we use. On top of this we constantly review our subcontractor's technical protection and security measures to ensure that they are adequate. For questions or clarifications, please contact privacy@barium.se
General Terms & Conditions Barium Live Download as pdf (eng) or Download as pdf (swe) - Last updated 2018-04-25
General Terms & Conditions Consulting Services Download as pdf (eng) or Download as pdf (swe) - Last updated 2018-04-25
Data Processor Agreement (DPA) Download as pdf (eng) or Download as pdf (swe) - Last updated 2020-08-25
Privacy Policy for Sales & Marketing Purpose Last updated 2018-04-25
Privacy Policy for Barium & Our PlatformsDownload as pdf (eng) - Last updated 2018-05-22
Barium Live enables you to have complete transparency throughout your entire workflows. Complex operations made easy.
